lisbon.net 2019-04-26

# Privacy policy - Civitatis.com

1.- Introduction and right to information

This website is property of Civitatis Tours S.L., (hereinafter, _“ **CIVITATIS** ”_) with Tax ID number B-86899440 and registered address at Coloreros 2, 28013, Madrid.

Protecting the security and privacy of your personal information is very important to CIVITATIS. Thus the Company fully complies with the current legislation on Data Protection so that your personal information is kept safe.

This data protection act regulates the access and use of the website service that CIVITATIS makes available to Users interested in the services offered by the Company.

If you wish to get in contact with our Data Protection Officer, you can send us an email at: [dpo@civitatis.com](mailto:dpo@civitatis.com).

2.-Why is CIVITATIS qualified to carry out personal data processing?

The personal information provided by the Users through the online register forms available on our Websites are collected by CIVITATIS to carry out the provision of the services offered on the Website.

In accordance with the applicable privacy legislation and its implementation, CIVITATIS, owner of the Websites, informs the User of the existence of an automated personal data file, duly registered in the General Register of the Spanish Data Protection Agency, created by CIVITATIS under its responsibility.

3.- Processing of personal data and how we use your information

CIVITATIS may collect the Users’ personal information through registration forms. The personal information requested by CIVITATIS may be used for the following purposes:

  1. The provision of services offered on the Website or put in contact the Users with our service providers that sometimes CIVITATIS offers through the Website as an intermediary.
  2. Send commercial communications to Users by letter, telephone, e-mail, SMS/MMS, instant messaging or other equivalent means of communication related to the services provided by CIVITATIS, on the condition that the User has given his/her consent to this purpose of personal data processing.

Likewise, the User consents to the processing of his or her data for the purposes of profiling, as well as for the segmentation of his or her data. The purpose of the processing may be used to analyze and draw up statistics to check the traffic and use of the Website by Users and to determine their tastes and preferences to send them promotional information in accordance with their interests.

In addition, and in accordance with the request made by the user, CIVITATIS could share your personal details with third parties which collaborate with CIVITATIS (travel agents) to be able to attend to the user's request. This is in accordance with the law established in article 6.1 b) of the EU regulation 2016/679 from the European Parliament and the council of the 27th April 2016, relative to the protection of a natural person regarding the use of personal data and the free circulation of said data.

4.- Accuracy of the data and mandatory or optional information provided by the User

The User guarantees that the personal data provided is true and is responsible for notifying CIVITATIS of any changes of his or her personal information. The User is responsible for the veracity of the data provided and the Entity has the right to no longer provide a service to any User who has provided false information, without prejudice to other actions stipulated by law. 

It is recommended to take the utmost care in matters of Data Protection using security tools. CIVITATIS cannot be held responsible for any theft, modification or loss of illicit data.

5.- Rules of conduct

CIVITATIS will cancel the registrations of Users who: **(i)** include or promote illegal, immoral, obscene or harmful material; **(ii)** promote any type of discrimination; **(iii)** Submit bulk, junk, or spam e-mail or newsgroup communications when they have not been requested; **(iv)** violate any third parties’ intellectual or industrial property rights. Likewise, the User will refrain from using and collecting data from the mailing lists that can be accessed through the information and services contained in the Website. These are used for carrying out activities for promotional or advertising purposes. The User will also refrain from sending any kind of commercial communications, which have not been requested or previously permitted by CIVITATIS and / or the Users of the Website.

The personal information provided will be kept by CIVITATIS as long as the User does not express his or her wish to unsubscribe from the services of CIVITATIS and receive information on products of the company.

6.- Exercising the right to access, rectify, cancel or oppose the Personal Data held on the file

The User has the right to **(i)** access his/her personal information, as well as **(ii)** request the rectification of inaccurate information or, where necessary, **(iii)** request deleting his or her personal information, as well as **(iv)** request the limitation of the processing of his/her information, **(v)** oppose the processing of his/her information, and **(vi)** exercise the right to be forgotten and **(vii)** request the information’s portability.

To exercise these rights, the User must prove his/her identity to CIVITATIS by sending a photocopy of his/her National Identity Card or any other legally valid documentation.

The User can exercise his/her rights by sending an email to [civitatis@civitatis.com](mailto:civitatis@civitatis.com), indicating his/her request. 

The User may also send his or her request by mail to the following address:

**CIVITATIS TOURS S.L.**

Calle Coloreros 2

28013, Madrid.

Without prejudice to any other administrative resource or legal action, the User shall have the right to file a complaint before a Control Authority, in the Member State in which the User resides, works or where the alleged infringement took place, if he or she considers that the processing of his/her personal information is not used in accordance with the law and if he/she is not satisfied with the exercise of his/her rights. The Control Authority that has received the complaint shall inform the complainant of the outcome of the complaint and the outcome of the complaint.

7.- Security

The protection of the privacy and personal information of all its customers and visitors is extremely important to CIVITATIS. Therefore, CIVITATIS will do anything in its power to prevent Users’ personal information from being misused. Only authorized personnel can access your personal information.

CIVITATIS maintains the security levels of personal information protection in accordance with the applicable regulations and has established all the technical means at its disposal to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of all the data that Users provide through the Websites, without prejudice to informing you that the Internet’s security measures are not impregnable.

CIVITATIS undertakes to comply with the duty of secrecy and confidentiality with respect to personal information in accordance with the applicable legislation, as well as to provide a secure processing in all international cessions and transfers that may occur.

8.- Queries

If you have any queries related to this privacy policy, please contact us at [civitatis@civitatis.com](mailto:civitatis@civitatis.com).

9.- Acceptance and Consent

The User declares that he/she has been informed of the conditions regarding their data protection and accept and consent to their personal information being processed by CIVITATIS for the purposes already indicated in this Privacy Policy.
